Guide to the Dimock Gallery records, 1963-2011 RG0087
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Dimock Gallery records
1963-2011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Dimock Gallery
RG0087
40 Linear Feet 24 record center boxes, 4 document boxes, 2 slim document boxes, 1 flat box
Collection includes M.F.A. thesis photos, exhibition schedules and programs, and brochures.
Restrictions on Access
Series 4 is closed to research for 25 years from date of record creation.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from the Dimock Gallery. Series 7 was transfered in 2017 [2017.054].
Historical or Biographical Note
The Dimock Gallery of The George Washington University resides in the Lisner Auditorium, built in 1941. The Dimock (named for Susan Dimock Catalini, a University benefactor) opened in 1966, and is an educational gallery which provides a professional setting for the display of art on The George Washington University campus. With the active support of Department of Fine Arts and Art History students, the Dimock Gallery's mission provides for a "hands-on" experience for curating and presenting their creative endeavors. Ongoing student and faculty participation provides a forum for students to curate, display, and critique their creative efforts, and creates a learning environment in which students can organize exhibitions and learn about exhibition design with the advice of faculty and curators. From time to time, exhibitions will be staged in conjunction with Lisner Auditorium performances, such as Flamenco Festivals, other international collaborations, and academic programs.
Douglas Teller joined the faculty at GW in 1962 and retired after a long and successful teaching career in 1995. A professor of design and printmaking, he taught courses in design, serigraphy, and watercolor as well. He forged new ground for printmaking within the University and for the Washington area, serving as a member of the Board of Directors of the Society of Washington Printmakers. When John Russell Mason, University Librarian and Curator of Art, retired in 1966, a void was created. It was filled by Professor Teller, who became the Dimock Gallery's first curator (1966-69). He established the university's gallery as a showcase for the university and Washington area, augmenting the contemporary arts holdings, and acknowledging GW's cultural and educational responsibilities to its students and local artists. Teller was succeeded as Curator of Art by Evelyn Stolte (September 1969-December 1971 and September 1972-May 1973); Gail Obenreder (January-June 1972); Donald C. Kline (June 1973-June 1975); and Lenore Miller (July 1975- ).
N.B. This history note was written in 2005
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include M.F.A. thesis photos, exhibition schedules and programs, and brochures. They range in date from 1963 to 2011, and were transferred to the University Archives by the Director of the Dimock Gallery. Note: Not all series are processed. Ask staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized into seven series: Exhibit materials; Brochures, schedules of exhibits; Exhibit schedule and programs; Photos; Records (1963-200); Records undated and Exhibition files.
Lisner Auditorium; Dimock Gallery; Exhibitions; Art; Washington (D.C.); Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); Teller, Douglas H.; Dimock, Susan Whitney; George Washington University
- Exhibit materials, ca.1980-89; RG0087 Series 1; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of exhibit materials on the Lenthall Houses, F Street Club, 2000 Penn. Avenue. They range in date from c.1980-89, and were transferred to University Archives in 1991.
  - Opening Reception Program, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Inventory of Materials, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Pictures from the Exhibit, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Pictures from the Exhibit, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lenthall Townhouses, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 2000 Pennsylvania Ave, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Three Sites- GWU Heritage, 08/1983--10/1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    General note
    Text, Letters, Memos, Etc.
  - Underwood House, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alexander Ray House (F Street Club), undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Buildings Reborn, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Labels from the Exhibit, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Map, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Folio
- Brochures, schedules of exhibits, 1966-2000; RG0087 Series 2; 1 Linear foot (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series consists of brochures, schedules, and programs from Dimock Gallery exhibits, and range in date from 1966-2000. They were transferred to University Archives in 2001.
  - Exhibition Schedule, 1966-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Dimock Gallery Exhibits, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Exhibit schedule and programs, 1995-1996; RG0087 Series 3; 0.5 Linear feet
  This series consists of exhibition schedule and programs, and range in date from 1995-96. They were transferred to University Archives in 1996.
  - Exhibition Schedule, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Angles of Vision program, 03/7/1996-03/27/1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - GW BMOC program, 06/21/1995-09/09/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Oleg Kudryashov Program, 09/21/1995-10/25/1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Victorian Sentiment and American History Painting Program, 12/14/1995-02/22/1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - MEA Thesis Candidate Show, 05/09/1996-05/31/1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Photos, 1986-2003; RG0087 Series 4; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of Master of Fine Arts thesis photos, and range in date from 1970-87. They were transferred to University Archives in 1991.
  This series has a container list in electronic form, please ask staff for assistance.
- Records, 1963-2000; RG0087 Series 5; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains memorandums, programs, a notebook, grant proposals, and a list of collections. They range in date from 1963 to 1983. They concern the University art collection, John Russel Mason, the Peale family exhibit, the Peale portraits of George Washington, and presidential portraits.
  - Dimock Gallery, 1977-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dimock Gallery - annual reports, 1977-1979, 1977-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dimock Gallery - brochures, 1968-2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dimock Gallery - grants, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - George Washington's Portraits, 1963-1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - University art collection, 1963-01/28/1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Records, unknown; Series 6 (Flat box 2)
- Exhibition files, 1966-2011; Series 7; 36 Linear Feet 24 record center cartoons
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains exhibition files produced by the Dimock Gallery dating between 1966-2011.
  Arrangement
  Material is arranged in the orginal order.
  Dimock Gallery; Exhibitions
  - Exhibition files, 1966-1970 (Box 1)
    This box contains the following materials: • Oliphant - Oct. 1970 • Mon-Ying Chow (Mrs.) • Vault Show, 1970 • Phillipine Artists, 1970, June 12 - 19 • Yolanda Mohalyi, May 4 – 29, 1970 • Fine Arts Faculty, April 1 – May 1, 1970 • History of American art course: • Student Show Feb 19 – March 20, 1970 • Contemporary Makonde sculpture • Washington Print Club Dec. 4 – Jan, 1970 • Chronological File - 1969-1970 • Patrons Program, 1969-1970 • American Porcelain Nov. 5 – Dec. 1, 1969 • Film Festival Oct. 6 – 31, 1969 • La Paradis de L'Enfant Sept 4 – Oct. 1, 1969 • Art Director's Club of Washington June 11-30, 1969 • Society of Washington Printmakers, May 6 – 29, 1969 • Elaine Gates, April 1 – 30, 1969 • 5th Annual Invitational 3/11-28 – 1969 • Sidney Goodman, Feb 6 – 28, 1969 • Washington Kiln Club Dec. 6 – 20, 1968 • Student Show and Sale Nov. 7 – Dec. 1, 1968 • Master of Fine Arts Theses Oct. 11 – Nov. 6, 1968 • Sampling of GW Permanent Collection, Sept. 9 – Oct. 10, 1968 • 4th Annual Invitational, May 4 – 28, 1968: Negro Artists in Washington • Society of Washington Artists, April 5 – May 3, 1968 • Leo Manso Exhibit, March 7 – 29, 1968 • Alumni Show, 1968 • Society of Washington Printmakers, February 4 – 29, 1968 • Student Exhibit and Sale, December 7 – 15, 1967 • Jack Levine – "Three Penny Opera", November 9 – 30, 1967 • Byron Burford Exhibit, October 4 – November 6, 1967 • Art of the Far East, September 13-29, 1967 • Sculptures, Jose Buscaglia, May 11 – June 11, 1967 • Spring Student Art Show, May 5 – May 25, 1967 • Jean K. Marsh – "Nature Dynamics", April 3-27, 1967, In Library • Student Exhibit and Sale, December 7 – 14, 1966 • 3rd Annual GW Invitational, March 9 – April 28, 1967 • Etchings and Lithographs, J Pennell, February 20 – March 3, 1967 • Design at GWU, January 11 – January 31, 1967 • Student Exhibit and Sale, December 7 – December 14, 1966 • Society of Washington Artists, November 18 – December 5, 1966 • Fine Arts Faculty: GWU & Corcoran, October 26 – November 14, 1966
  - Exhibition files, 1970-1974 (Box 2)
    This box contains the following materials: • Front, not in folder: List of "The Dimock Gallery Exhibition Schedule, 1966 – Present" [1974] • Hereward Lester Cooke Found. Exhibition & Auction, Oct. 29-30-31-Nov. 1, 1974 • Recent Acquisitions, October 14 – 23 [1974] • Sculpture in Living Places, Sept. 11 – Oct. 11, 1974 • Exhibition Schedule, Press Releases – 1974-75 • Goodman & Rogers, July 15 – 29, 1974 • The Artist at Work…, June 3 – July 10, 1974 • One Man Show, Taro Ichihashi, May 16 – 31, 1974 • 1974 Kreeger Awards Show, March 20 – 30, 1974 • MFA Thesis Show, April 22 – May 4, 1974 • The Faculty's Hang-Ups, April 4 – 19, 1974 • 7 at 730, March 4 – 15, 1974 • A Generation of Alumni Artists, Feb. 6 - 28, 1974, Invitational Show – GW Alumni Artists • Rudolph Heintze, Jan 7-30, 1974 • Wall Hangings Show – Dec. 13-16, 1973, "Midnight in Flight" • Annual Student Christmas Show, November 28 – Dec. 19, 1973 • The Salon – 19th Century Works from the GWU Collection • Exhibition Returns/Pick Ups, Cont. Works & Salon • The University Collects: Contemporary Works from the Permanent Collection, October 3–23, 1973 • Projected Exhibition, '73 – 74 • Fine Arts Faculty Show, 5-23 February 1973 • MFA Thesis Show, April 12-26, 1973 • Kreeger Show, 19-30 March 1973 • Exhibition Schedule – 1973/74 • Joseph Pennell Etchings, Winter 1972-73 • Contemporary art in the collection, Fall 1972 • Masters Thesis – May 3 – May 17 [1972] • Student – April12-26 [1972] • Kreeger – Mar. 15 – Mar. 29, 1972 • Washington Before 1910: Photographs from the W. Lloyd Wright Collection, February 10 – March 3, 1972 • Society of Washington Printmakers, Jan. 5/6 – Jan. 28, 1972 • Preszler – Dec.8/9 – Dec. 31, 1971 • Japanese Prints, Nov. 10/11 – Dec. 3, 1971 • P.I.E., May 1971 • Yellin, March 1971 • Portraits – University History, Sesquicentennial – Feb. 8-23, 1971 • Washington Kiln Club Show, 6-29 January 1971 • Student Show, GWU, 1970-71 • Sale of Student Prints
  - Exhibition files, 1974-1976 (Box 3)
    This box contains the following materials: • Gifts and Recent Acquisitions, January 22 – February 20, 1976 [Exhibition] • Antarctica – S.I.T.E.S., Jan. 14-19, 1976 • Arthur Hall Smith Exhibition, Dec. 11 – Jan. 9, 1976 • In the Spirit of Expressionism, Nov. 11 – Dec. 5, 1975 • Development Show: Jack Burns, Oct. 16-31, 1975 • Student Show, Oct. 1975 • Pennell Etchings & Lithographs, Sept. 10 – Oct. 10, 1975 • Summer Thesis Show, August 4 – 29, 1975 • June 4 – 30, 1975, Zeki Findikoglu: The Storyteller • MFA Thesis Show 1975, April 22 – May 20, 1975 • David Lloyd Kreeger Awards, April 2-18, 1975 • Invitational Show: Inner Exploration, March 5-28, 1975 • The Ethnic Art-The Living Tradition, Feb. 5 – 28, 1975 • James Twitty, Jan. 8-31, 1975 • Exhibition Schedule 1975/76 • Annual Student Christmas Show, Dec. 4-18, 74 • Alumni Collections, Nov. 7-26, 1974
  - Exhibition files, 1976-1978 (Box 4)
    This box contains the following materials: • Exhibition file list • Feb. 25 – March 25, 1978, Handicapped Art Exhibition • An American Architecture…, Dec. 14, 1977 – Jan. 20, 1978 • Student Christmas Show and Auction, Nov. 9 – Dec. 9, 1977 • MFA Thesis – Summer '77, August 31 – Sept. 16, 1977 • 10th Anniversary Exhibition, Area Invitational Painting, May 19 – June 17, 1977 • MFA Thesis Show, Spring 1977, April 20 – May 9, 1977 • Annual Awards Show, March 28 – April 8, 1977 • Teaching Sculpture at GW, March 2-18, 1977 • Metaphorical Trends in Contemporary Polish Art, Feb. 3-28, 1977 • Penn. Ave–Wash Circle to White House, Jan. 17-28, 1977 • Edvard Munch: Graphics, S.I.T.E.S. 12/20 – 1/15/77 [1976-1977] • Student Xmas Show & Sale, Nov. 8 – Dec. 7, 1976 • French Contemporary Arts Fest., Oct. 11-31, 1976 • The Painterly Vision, September 8-30, 1976 • Creative Growth, July 6-28, 1976, Himmelfarb Library • Summer Thesis Show, July 29 – Aug. 13, 1976 • G.W.-B.M.O.C., June 15 – July 15, 1976 • Bicentennial Show, May 17 – July 15, 1976 • Art Directors Club Show, May 16 – June 4, 1976 • MFA Thesis Show, April 15 – May 10, 1976 • Faculty Show, April 1 – 14, 1976 • Awards Show, March 3-31, 1976
  - Exhibition files, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
    This box contains the following materials: • MFA Thesis Show Spring 1980, May 1 – 28, 1980 • Annual Awards Show, April 3 – April 25, 1980 • Faculty Hang-Ups No. 4, February 21 – March 21, 1980 • Edgar Tafel lecture, Feb. 21, 1980 • MFA Thesis Show, Jan. 24 – Feb. 15, 1980 • Selected Paintings by Mitchell Jamieson, Dec. 13, 1979 – Jan. 11, 1980 • Annual Student Show-GWU Art Department, 11/21-12/8/79 • Internship Seminar, November 15, 1979 • Summer in Brittany, GWU, 1979, Sept. 20 – Oct. 5, 1979 • Dr. Kenneth Garlick Lecture, Sept. 21, 1979 • Lowell Nesbitt, Aug. 16 – Sept. 14, 1979 • International Museum Day Open House, May 18, 1979 • Michael Clark: Picture Windows, May 23 – June 29, 1979 • MFA Thesis Show, Spring 1979, May 3-18, 1979 • 1979 Annual Awards Show, April 11 – April 27, 1979 • Douglas H Teller & H. Irving Gates, 2-person faculty, March 1-30, 1979 • 400 Years of Art: GW Collects, Jan. 25 – Feb. 23, 1979 • Waldemar Swierzy, Poster Artist, Jan. 25, 1979 o discussion in Lower Lisner Auditorium • German Expressionism: Die Brucke, Dec. 14, 1978 – Jan. 12, 1979 • Nov. 30, 1978, Oskar Kokoschka Lecture, Count Bethusy-Huc of Vienna • Annual Student Show – GWU Art Department, Nov. 16 – Dec. 8, 1978 • Luis Barragan Lecture, Thurs. Oct. 19 & Wed., Oct. 25, 1978 • MFA Thesis Show, April 19 – May 12, 1978 • Textural Renderings: Works on Paper, May 24 – June 30, 1978 • MFA Thesis Show Summer 1978, Aug. 15 – Sept. 15, 1978 • 20th Century Mexican Prints from the Library of Congress Collection, Oct. 4 – Nov. 10, 1978 • Awards Show, March 29 – April 14, 1978 • Faculty Hang-Ups #3, March 1 – 24, 1978 • Summer in Brittany – GW 1977, Jan. 25 – Feb. 24, 1978
  - Exhibition files, 1980-1982 (Box 6)
    This box containes the following materials: • MFA Thesis Show, Winter 1982, 1/14/82 – 1/29/82 • Romance & Imagination: The Etchings of Max Klinger, Dec. 10, 1981 – Jan. 8, 1982 • Annual Student Show, 11/12/81 – 12/4/81 • U.S. Grant III Collection: Selections, 10/7/81 – 11/6/81 • Configurations: A Selection of Contemporary Photographs, June 18 – Sept. 18, 1981 • MFA Thesis Show, Spring '81, April 30 – May 22, 1981 • Annual Awards Show, April 2 – 24, 1981 • Fuller Griffith/William Woodward, Feb. 26 – March 20, 1981 • MFA Thesis Show, Jan. 15 – 30, 1981 • Joseph Metivier Memorial Fine Arts Faculty Exhibition, Feb. 5-20, 1981 • Know What You See: Process & Progress in Conservation, Dec. 11, 1980 – Jan. 9, 1981 • Annual Student Show, Nov. 13 – Dec. 3, 1980 at Dimock Gallery & GSA Building • Themes & Images in Pre-Columbian Art: Spear & Weiser Collections, Oct. 9 – Nov. 7, 1980 • Architectural Ceramics, June 4 – July 18, 1980 • Architectural Ceramics Artists' File, June 4 – July 18, 1980
  - Exhibition files, 1982-1984 (Box 7)
    This box contains the following materials: • MFA Thesis Candidate Show, Spring 1984, May 3 – 25, 1984 • Annual Awards Show, April 12 – 27, 1984 • GW Fine Arts Faculty Exhibition, March 8 – April 4, 1984 • Annual Student Show, Feb. 16 – March 2, 1984 • MFA Thesis Candidate Show, Winter 1984, Jan. 12 – Feb. 10, 1984 • The Intimate Scale: Paintings from the Phillips Collection, Nov. 10, 1983 – Jan. 6, 1984 • Selections from the W. Lloyd Wright Collection of Washingtoniana, Oct. 20 – Nov. 2, 1983 • MFA Thesis Candidate Show, May 5 – 27, 1983 • Annual Awards Show, April 7 – 29, 1983 • Jerry Lake: Photographs, Frank Wright: Paintings & Prints, March 3 – 30, 1983 • The GWU Fine Arts Faculty Exhibition, Feb. 3 – 25, 1983 • The Fine Art of Private Commissions, Dec. 15, 1982 – Jan. 28, 1983 • Annual Student Show, Nov. 18 – Dec. 10, 1982 • Enamels '82, Oct. 20 – Nov. 12, 1982 • GWU Art Alumni Invitational Exhibition, Sept. 16 – Oct. 15, 1982 • Master Photographs from Washington Collections, June 3 – July 16, 1982 • MFA Thesis Candidate Show, Spring 1982, April 29 – May 28, 1982 • Annual Awards Show, April 1 – 23, 1982 • GWU Fine Arts Faculty Exhibition, Feb. 25 – March 24, 1982 • GW 250th Birthday Exhibition, 2/4/82 – 2/19/82
  - Exhibition files, 1984-1986 (Box 8)
    This box contains the following materials: • GW Fine Arts Faculty Exhibition, Feb. 27 – Mar. 26, 1986 • Clarice Smith, Jan. 15 – Feb. 21 1986 • Joseph Pennell, Dec. 12, 1985 – Jan. 10, 1986 • Annual Student Show, Nov. 14 – Dec. 6, 1985 • Turker Ozdogan/Arthur Hall Smith, Oct. 10 – Nov. 8, 1985 • Tradition and Innovation: A Washington Area Invitational, Sept. 12 – Oct. 4, 1985 • Surface and Ornament, July 10 – Aug. 30, 1985 • Envelope: "Promotional Material from Formica" [accompanies "Surface and Ornament"] • MFA Thesis Candidate Shows, Group I: May 2-17, Group II: May 23 – June 7, 1985 • Annual Awards Show, April 4-26, 1985 • GW Fine Arts Faculty Exhibition, Feb. 12 – March 27, 1985 • MFA Thesis Candidate Show, Winter 1985, Jan. 17 – Feb. 8, 1985 • Charles Pollock, Dec. 13, 1984 – Jan. 11, 1985 • Annual Student Show, Nov. 15 – Dec. 7, 1984 • Contemporary Photographs from the GW Permanent Collection, Oct. 18 – Nov. 9, 1984 • GW Art Alumni Exhibition, Sept. 12 – Oct. 10, 1984 • Photos – Alumni Exhibit, Sept. 12 – Oct. 10, 1984
  - Exhibition files, 1986-1987 (Box 9)
    This box contains the following materials: • Annual Student Show, Nov. 12 – Dec. 3, 1987 • Graphic Designers: Visual Communications Alumni, Sept. 10 – Oct. 8, 1987 • MFA Thesis Candidate Show, May 7-28, 1987 • Annual Awards Show, April 9 – April 30, 1987 • Constance Costigan/Sam Molina, Mar. 5 – April 1, 1987 • GW Fine Art Faculty Show, Feb. 5-26, 1987 • Catalog Copy, Yochelson Show • Winter Thesis, Jan. 15 – Jan. 29, 1987 • Annual Student Show, Nov. 13 – Dec. 5, 1986 • Photographs: Exhibitions, GW Faculty Collects, 10/16 – 11/7/86 • GW Faculty Collects, Oct. 16 – Nov. 7, 1986 • 3rd GW Art Alumni Exhibition, September 11 – Oct. 10, 1986 • MFA Thesis Show, Spring 1986, • Annual Awards Show, April 3 – 25, 1986 • NOTE: box inventory lists "200. Tough Realism: An Invitational Painting Exhibition, Oct. 15 – Nov. 5, 1987" as bring in Dimock Gallery Exhibition Files
  - Exhibition files, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
    This box contains the following materials: • MFA Spring Thesis Candidate Show, May 4 – May 25, 1989 • Annual Awards Show, April 6 – April 27, 1989 • GW Fine Arts Faculty Exhibition, (Full-time & Part-time)March 9 – March 28, 1989 • Jeffrey Stephanic and Douglas H Teller: February 9 – March 2, 1989 • MFA Winter Thesis Candidate Show, January 12 – February 2, 1989 • Annual Student Show, November 17 [1988]– January 5, 1989 • 4th GW Art Alumni Exhibition: October 14 – November 11, 1988 • MFA Thesis Candidate Show, Spring, May 5 – May 27, 1988 • Annual Awards Show, April 7 – April 28, 1988 • Michael Green: Posthumous Show, Mar. 17 – Mar. 30, 1988 • GW Fine Arts Faculty Show, Feb. 11 – Mar. 11, 1988 • MFA Thesis Candidate Show, Winter, Jan. 14 – Feb. 4, 1988 • Special Events, 1988-89 (Focus '89)
  - Exhibition files, 1989-1992 (Box 11)
    This box contains the following materials: • Exhibitions 219, 220, 226, 228, 230, 233, 237 • 219 – Annual Student Show – 11/16 – 12/7/1989 • 220 – Patrons and Collectors: Works from the GW Permanent Collection (including works from the Murray Bring Collection) - 12/14/1989 – 1/18/1990 • 226 – Structural Symbols: Photographs of New York City (GW Permanent Collection and selected loans curated by Francine Zorn Trachtenberg) – 9/6/1990 – 10/15/1990 • 228 – Diverse Themes: GW Alumni invitational Painting Exhibition, 12/6/1990 – 1/3/1991 • 230 – HI Gates: Knights of the Rising Sun: Japanese Armour as an art form & Fuller Griffith: Works on paper (2-person Fine Arts Faculty Exhibition) 2/7/1991 – 3/26/1991 • 233 - Temples of Gold • 237 – African American Artists in Washington: Selections from the Perm. Coll. of the Howard Univ. Gallery of Art and the GWPC, 12/12/1991 – 1/2/1992
  - Exhibition files, 1990-1991 (Box 12)
    This box contains the following materials: • Annual Student Show 11/7 - 12/5/91 • Bruno Lucchesi, 11/11 – 11/15/1991 – Smith Distinguished Visiting Prof. in Fine Arts • Special President Bush Reception 10/27/91 – special exh. in Dimock Gallery for Pres. G.H.W. Bush and wife • Cystic Fibrosis Art Auction – Designs for Genes (Exh. 235) Susan Tolchin (members of Friends involved) 10/22 – 10/23/1991 • Lithograph Review, 1991, Tokyo + Washington, DC – (Exh. 234) Print exchange, group exhibition (ref: Scip Barnhart) • Spring MFA Thesis Candidate Show 5/2 – 5/23/1991, Exh. 232 • Annual Awards Show 4/4 – 4/25/1991, Exh 231 • Annual Student Show, 11/8 – 11/29/1990, Exh. 227 • Nelson Shanks, 10/29 – 11/1/90, Smith Distinguished Visiting Prof., Fine Arts • Sculpture: The Studio Tradition at GW, Faculty and Alumni Artists, 6/5 – 7/31/1990, Exh. 225 • MFA Spring Thesis Candidate Show, 5/3 – 5/24/1990, Exh. 224 • Annual Awards Show, 4/5 – 4/26/1990, Exh. 223 • GW Fine Arts Faculty Show (Full-Time), 3/8 – 3/27/1990, Exh. 222 • MFA Winter Thesis Candidate Show, 1/25 – 3/1/1990, Exh. 221
  - Exhibition files, 1992-1993 (Box 13)